（忆往昔）
死亡骑士 他会出现在那里
Death … he's gonna be there.
我知道你要这个
I understand you want this.
但是有条件的
There are conditions.
你知道你骗不了死亡骑士
You know you can't cheat death.
我觉得它不是在杀人
I don't think it's killing people.
不过是在人们大限将近时 带走他们
I think it's taking them when their time is just up.
死神
A reaper.
你比我上次见到的那个死神可美多了
You're much prettier than the last reaper I met.
这就是上次来找你的那个死神
So, this is the reaper that came after you.
- 迪恩 - 苔莎
- Dean. - Tessa.
- 巴尔萨泽 - 为什么你要买下人的灵魂
- Balthazar. - Why you buying up human souls?
你知道灵魂价值几何
Do you have any idea what souls are worth?
又拥有多么强大的能量吗
What power they hold?
只是想确定 关于要回你的灵魂
Just making sure that you're not having second thoughts.
你没有半点犹豫
about getting your soul back.
萨姆的灵魂和米迦勒还有路西法一起
Sam's soul has been locked in the cage.
被关在笼子里
with Michael and Lucifer.
如果我们强行
If we try to force.
把那个残废的东西塞到萨姆体内
that mutilated thing down Sam's gullet,
结果可能会非常惨烈
it could be catastrophic.
他需要自己的灵魂
He needs his soul.
我们把它弄回来
Look, we get it back.
如果出现什么复杂情况
And if there are complications,
我们再想办法处理
then we will figure out a way to deal with those, too.
（如今）
开什么玩笑呢
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
我在 找…
Hi, I'm, uh, looking for…
沿这条路到后面
Follow all the way back.
到后面
All the way back.
迪恩·温彻斯特
Dean Winchester?
你一定就是罗伯特博士了吧
You must be Dr. Robert?
孩子 给你父亲缝伤口的次数我都数不清了
Son, I stitched up your daddy more times than I can count,
跟你说
Let me tell you.
见到你真是太好了
It's good to see you.
当然这都是很久以前的事
Of course that was ages ago, go back.
那时候我还有行医执照呢
when I still have my medical lisence.
这边走
Right this way.
我不是个…
Well, you know, I'm, uh,
我没洁癖 但是…
I'm no germ freak, but…
这里租金便宜
Rent's cheap.
伊娃 我的助手
Eva, my assistant.
躺这边来
Hop right up.
你 你做这个很多次了吗
N-now, you … you have, uh, done this a lot?
那是相当多了
Oh, many, many times.
那你的… 成功率是多少
And your…Success rate?
相当出色 差不多有75%
Oh, excellent … almost 75%.
那么 我们先做好准备工作如何
So, should we get the, uh, preliminaries out of the way?
好的 好的
Yeah. Uh, yeah, right.
那么…
So…
听着 万一…
Listen, if, uh, something…
出事了
Goes wrong?
是啊
Yeah. Uh…
你能帮我寄这封信吗
Would you mail this for me, please?
当然
Sure.
我还以为你有东西要留给弟弟萨姆呢
Would've thought you had something for your brother, Sam.
如果我不能回来
If I don't make it back,
我说什么对他来说都是瞎扯淡
nothing I say is gonna mean a damn thing to him.
傲娇个啥
Don't be a baby.
对病人好点会死吗
You know, a little bedside manner would be nice.
准备好了吗
Are we ready? Hmm?
你有三分钟的时间
You've got three minutes.
没有脉搏 没有窦性心律
No pulse, no sinus rhythm.
他挂了
He's dead.
真开心
Good times.
最好能行得通
This better work.
[咒语]
迪恩
Dean?
搞什么鬼呢
What the hell?
我勒个去 还真管用了
What do you know? It worked.
我刚刚正在苏丹
I was in the Sudan!
你召唤我过来…
What's with yanking me ov…
- 等等 你怎么会死 - 苔莎 帮个忙
- Wait, why are you dead? - Tessa, I need a favor.
开什么玩笑 你挂掉就为找我帮…
Oh, you're kidding. You died to ask me …
- 跟你老大说我要跟他聊聊 - 不行
- Tell your boss I need to talk to him. - No.
- 求你了 - 你胆子怎么这么大
- Please? - Where do you get the nerve?
非常时期嘛
Desperate times.
只有他召唤我们的份 我们无法召唤他
He calls us. We don't call him.
- 那你就破例一次 - 我办不到
- You make an exception! - I can't.
- 不能还是不想 - 都有
- Can't or won't?! - Both!
好了 苔莎 非常感谢你
All right, Tessa. Thank you very much.
你好啊 迪恩
Hello, Dean.
[邪恶力量 第6季第11集]
我很忙的 迪恩 有话快说
I'm busy, Dean. Talk fast.
我手上有属于你的东西
I have something of yours.
你是指我的戒指吗
You mean my ring?
我记得是暂时借给你而已
I recall loaning you that temporarily.
好吧 如果你想要回它的话
Well, if you want it back …
抱歉 你以为我不知道你将它藏在哪吗
I'm sorry, you assume that I don't know where you've hidden it.
可算见识了刚愎自用却一无是处的你了
Now we've established you have hubris but no leverage,
你到底想干嘛
what is it you want?
路西法的牢笼
Lucifer's cage.
我知道你是为数不多能够打开它的人之一
I figure you're one of the few people that can actually jailbreak it.
是吗
Do you?
萨姆的灵魂被困在里面了
Sam's soul is stuck in that box.
- 我听说了 - 我们三弟也困在里面
- I've heard. - And our other brother is trapped in there, too.
米迦勒带他进去的
Michael rode him in.
迪恩 有话快说有屁快放吧
Dean, quit shuffling and deal.
我想让你把他们都救出来
I want you to get 'em both out.
只能二选一
Pick one.
- 什么 - 要萨姆的灵魂还是亚当的
- What?! - Sam's soul or Adam's.
- 但是 - 照规矩 我不带人类回来
- But… - As a rule, I don't bring people back.
我只能破例一次 绝不能有第二次
I might make an exception once, not twice.
所以 选吧
So…Pick.
萨姆
Sam.
他的灵魂已经在那儿呆了整整一年了
His soul has been in there for a year,
我也知道它已经…有损伤
and I understand that it's…damaged.
那叫四分五裂
Try flayed to the raw nerve.
你有没有什么办法可以…
Well, is there any way that you could, uh,
抹掉地狱所经历的那部分
I don't know, hack the hell part off?
4 3 2
Four, three, two…
时间到
Now.
再来一次
Again.
迪恩 迪恩 迪恩
Dean, Dean, Dean.
你觉得灵魂是什么
What do you think the soul is?
是个可以让你随便切的派吗
Some pie you can slice?
灵魂可以被鞭笞折磨 但永不会破碎
The soul can be bludgeoned, tortured, but never broken.
即使是我也办不到
Not even by me.
那一定还有其他办法吧
Well, there's got to be something.
也许吧
Maybe.
抹去那部分办不到 但我可以
Can't erase Sam's hell, but I can…
若你愿意 我能将它隔离在屏障之外
put it behind a wall, if you will.
屏障
A "Wall."
他大脑中一个抑制思绪潮涌的大坝
In his mind … a dam to hold back the tide.
那些记忆可谓十分不愉快
Nasty, those memories.
你不会想知道它们会怎样影响他
You don't want to know what they'll do to him.
相信我
Believe me.
好吧 一个屏障 听起来好极了
Okay, uh, a wall. Sounds good.
但那不是永久性的
But it's not permanent.
没错 没什么能持续到永远
She's right. Nothing lasts forever.
我的确是永生 但是
Well, I do, but…
好吧 现在有两个选择
Okay, so that's the choice …
没有灵魂的萨姆
Sam with no soul,
或者是脑子里有墙的萨姆
or Sam with some drywall.
而这面墙一旦倒塌
that if or when it collapses,
他就完了
he's…done?
是的
Yes.
动手吧
Do it.
我从未说过我会做
I never said I'd do it.
那我们一直在讨论毛啊
Well, then what the hell have we been talking about?
这是你的奖励
Your prize.
如果你赌赢了
If you win the wager.
好吧 赌什么
Great. What's the bet?
别翻白眼 迪恩 很不礼貌
Don't roll your eyes, Dean. It's impolite.
把我的戒指拿来 戴上
Now, when you fetch my ring, put it on.
什么
What?
我要你扮演一天我的角色
I want you to be me for one day.
你认真的么
Are you serious?
不 我这是使劲儿吐槽呢
No, I'm being incredibly sarcastic.
伊娃 肾上腺素
Eva, adrenaline!
24小时之内取下戒指的话
Take the ring off before the 24 hours are up,
你就输了
and you lose.
萨姆就没灵魂了 清楚了吗
No soul for Sam. Clear?
好吧 清楚了
Okay. Yes.
但是 为什么啊
But…but why?
很简单 迪恩 因为
Simple, Dean. Because …
感谢摩西（《圣经》中犹太人古代领袖）
Oh, thank Moses.
你不能多让我死五秒钟吗
You couldn't have given me five more seconds?
孩子 你死了七分钟了
Son, you were gone for seven minutes.
- 真的吗 - 对啊
- I was? - Mm-hmm.
我还以为你活不了了呢
I thought for sure Death had you by the twins.
- 你什么 - 听我说啊
- You what?! - Just hear me out.
迪恩 我听过小卡和克劳力说
I heard Cass and Crowley when they said.
我要么死要么生不如死
it would either kill me or turn me to jello, Dean!
我听够了
I heard enough!
- 死亡说他能建一个屏障 - 屏障
- Death said he can put up a wall. - A wall?
对对 屏障 就是基本上
Yes, yes, a wall … that … that, basically,
- 能让你忘记地狱 - 真的吗
- you wouldn't remember hell. - Really?
真的
Really.
永远忘记 像病一样被治愈了
For good? Like a cure?
不是被治愈了
No, it's not a cure. It…
他说能持续一生
He said it could last a lifetime.
很好 就这样玩弄我的性命
Great. So, playing pretty fast and loose with my life here,
- 是吧 迪恩 - 我在努力救你的命
- don't you think, Dean? - I'm trying to save your life!
正是 迪恩 这是我的命
Exactly, Dean! It's my life!
是我的命 我的灵魂
It's my life, it's my soul.
你的计划要是出了什么差错
And it sure as hell ain't your head that's gonna explode.
你的脑袋反正不会爆炸
when this whole scheme of yours goes sideways!
我只是很好奇
Just curious.
我猜 死亡骑士做这一切
I presume death's not doing this.
不是他良心发现吧
out of the goodness of his heart.
你用什么来做交易
So what's your half of the deal?
抱歉 我没听清
I'm sorry. I didn't get that.
我得戴一天他的戒指
I have to wear the ring for a day.
他干嘛要你这么做
Why the hell would he want you to do that?
想爽一把什么的
Get his rocks off.
我不知道 但我已经答应了
I don't know. But I'm doing it.
你去哪里
Where you going?
我听完了你的话 我明白了
Look, I hear you, all right? I get it.
我只是需要一点时间来理理清楚
I just need a minute to wrap my head around it, all right?
找这个吗
Looking for this?
只是出来走走
Just taking a walk.
萨姆
Sam.
我是你哥哥
I'm your brother.
我不会让你受到伤害的
I'm not gonna let you get hurt.
- 我清楚我在做什么 - 如果你错了呢
- I know what I'm doing here. - What if you're wrong?
我不会让这件事出任何差错
I won't let it go wrong.
好吧
Fine.
「好吧」 那你
Fine? So, you're …
我信任你
So, I'm trusting you here.
勉强信任
Barely.
你确定
You sure?
你大权在握
You're the one with the compass, right?
别搞砸了
Just don't mess it up.
不会的
I won't.
看着他
Watch him.
你是不是还要拿枪指着我
So, is this the part where you pull a gun on me.
然后把我锁在密室里
and lock me in the panic room?
有这个必要吗
Do I have to?
没有
No.
我想迪恩只是做他份内的事
I guess Dean's got to do what he's got to do.
我们都是 孩子
Guess we all do, kid.
哥披挂上阵了
Well, here goes everything.
这年头 随便一个傻小子
They'll just let any slack-jawed haircut.
都能当死亡骑士了
be Death these days.
你今天魅力四射啊 对吧
Well, you're all charm today, aren't you?
话先说清楚 这样才能把麻烦降到最小
Let's be clear so that we get through this.
好轻松完成任务
with a minimum of screw-up.
我不喜欢这样
I don't like this.
而且现在我也不怎么喜欢你
And right now, I'm not crazy about you, either.
这是你老大的主意 不是我的
This is your boss' idea, not mine.
对 但你绝对称得上是
True. But you have a long history.
破坏大王了
of throwing a wrench in everything,
我们要遵守规则
so let's just stick to the rules.
- 行吗 - 什么规则
- Deal? - And the rules are?
接下来的二十四小时
For the next 24 hours,
你杀死那些死期临近的人
you kill everyone whose number's up.
- 我怎么知道什么人该… - 杀
- Well, how am I supposed to know who to… - Kill?
我有个名单
Yeah. I have a list.
- 我看看 - 不行
- Let me see. - No.
你触碰他们 他们就会死 我来收魂
You touch them, they die, I reap them.
清楚了吗
Are we clear?
清楚了吧
Yeah, I guess.
取下戒指 你就输了
Remove the ring, you lose.
摸鱼打混 你也输
Slack off, you lose.
- 听懂了吗 - 懂了
- Got it? - Yeah.
别搞砸了
Don't mess this up.
我不能老给你擦屁股
It's not my job to be your damn babysitter.
萨姆·温彻斯特
Sam…Winchester.
最好不是什么烂事儿
This had better be good.
这可是你做过最愚蠢的事情
Well, here's one for the list of dumbest things ever.
召唤想杀你的天使
Summon the angel who wants to kill you.
非常时期
Desperate times.
我需要你的帮助 巴尔萨泽
I need your help, Balthazar.
有意思
Interesting…
我们上次相遇
Since last time we met,
你想 想要什么来着
you wanted to … what was it?
对对 油炸我的翅膀 要「爽脆」
Oh, yes, yes … fry my wings "extra crispy."
那是个误会
Well, that was a misunderstanding.
误会的够深的啊
Some misunderstanding!
我需要一点建议
I need some advice.
- 建议 - 天使的建议
- Advice? - Angel advice.
那去问你的男朋友啊
Well, then go ask your boyfriend.
小卡无法帮我
Cass can't help me.
有没有一种咒语或者武器
I need to know if there's a spell or a weapon,
能让灵魂永远脱离肉体
anything that can keep a soul out … forever.
萨姆 怎么回事
What's going on, Sam?
给我用的
It's for me.
这样啊
Well.
情节真是扑朔迷离
The plot thickens.
萨姆 你的灵魂呢
Where's your soul, Sam?
我的天啊 不会还在…
Good god, no. It's not still…
真是啊
It is.
我哥哥找到了拿回我灵魂的方法
My brother found a way to put it back in me.
我不想要
I don't want it.
当然
No, you don't.
当然不要 话说小米和小路正折磨它
No, no, 'cause Michael and Lucy are hate-banging it.
折磨得起劲呢
as we speak.
- 你帮得了我吗 - 当然
- Can you help me? - Oh, yes.
问题是 我愿意吗
The question is, will I?
开个条件吧
Set your terms.
无偿提供
I'll do it for free.
免费
Free?
为什么
Why?
你看上去像个有为青年
Well, you seem like a capable young man.
我不介意你欠我点人情
I'd love to have you in my debt.
况且我必须承认 我对你哥可不怎么感冒
And I have to say, I'm not a fan of your brother,
看到他抓狂一定令人愉悦
so screwing him would delight me.
不管怎样 说正事 咒语
Anyway, to business. The spell, yes.
材料倒是很好找
So, finding the ingredients are easy enough,
但有一件比较棘手
but, uh, there's one tricky part, however.
恩
Okay.
你需要在你的皮囊上留下创伤
You need to scar your vessel.
什么意思
Meaning what?
需要有东西玷污它
Meaning something that so pollutes it,
让它不再适合灵魂居住
it renders it uninhabitable.
需要非常特别的东西
Calls for something very specific.
好 什么
Great. What?
弑父
Patricide.
我爸已经死了很多年了
My dad's been dead for years.
说白了 你需要你父亲的血
To be clear, um, you need the blood of your father,
但不一定是亲生父亲
but your father needn't be blood.
明白
Comprehended?
事先声明 人们死时
Just so you know, when people die,
他们很可能会问你问题
they might have questions for you.
不是问你 问死神
Well, you know, not you, but death.
像是
You mean like,
为什么贝蒂·怀特（著名长寿演员）都比我活得长
"How did Betty White outlast me?"
常见的是 这一切都算什么
"What's it all mean?" is popular.
那我会神奇地知道答案吗
And am I just gonna magically know?
不会
No.
那我他妈的该怎么回答
Then what the hell am I supposed to say?
拜托 总得说点什么吧
Oh, come on, give me something.
忍忍吧 随机应变
Suck it up. Comes with the gig.
利索点 利索点 拿钱来
Come on! Come on! Let's go!
他们看不见 也听不见你
They can't hear you. They can't see you.
在一旁看着就好了
Just let this play out.
我要带走哪个
Well, who am I taking?
静观其变
Wait and see.
哪一个
Which one?
你想让我毙了这小孩吗 速度点
You want me to shoot the kid?! Hurry up!
你以为我在开玩笑吗
Oh, you think I'm kidding?
还有柜台下面的抽屉
And don't forget the drawer under the register.
快啊 打开它
Come on, move it!
快点儿
Let's go!
蠢货
You idiot.
想什么呢 动手啊
Hello? Tick tock.
他现在痛苦难耐 是吧
He's in agonizing pain, right?
是啊
Uh, yes.
再等一下
Give me a minute.
为什么
Why?
主要是因为你是个混蛋
Mostly because you're a dick.
一路顺风 伙计
Enjoy the ride down, pal.
相信我 有你受的
Trust me … sauna gets hot.
也没那么难嘛
That wasn't so hard.
不是我说 他貌似是要心脏病突发吧
Call me crazy, but this smells like a heart attack.
还真猜着了
Lucky guess.
为什么
Why?
也许是奶酪太多了
You think maybe it was the extra cheese?
是啊 不过味道真不错
Yeah. It was good, though.
- 是在附近买的吗 - 迪恩
- Is that a local place? - Dean.
好吧 该上路了
Right. Uh, time to go, man.
抱歉
Sorry.
等等
Wait.
可不可以告诉我这一切都算什么
Will you tell me what it all means?
一切都是浮云
Everything is dust in the wind.
就这样
That's it?!
就一句歌词儿吗
A Kansas song?!
抱歉 他是新手
Sorry. He's new.
醒来的时候你就不在了 你去哪了
Woke up and you were gone. Where you been?
出去兜了兜风 没啥
Just driving around. No biggie.
- 喝吗 - 当然
- Drink? - Yeah, sure.
你先请 老大
After you, boss.
这个是你 我们去加州时照的
That's you when we went to California.
你那会儿才六岁
You were 6 then.
天 这张怎么还留着啊
God. We should burn that.
多可爱啊
You were adorable.
爸爸还是孩子
The dad or the kid?
孩子
Kid.
拜托 她才多大 十三岁
Come on. What is she, 13?
十二
She's 12.
这张呢
And that's…?
是你妈妈
That's your mom…
她像你这么大时照的
When she was your age.
他还有别的家人吗
This guy have any other family?
没了
No, not really.
这太惨了
Well, this is awesome.
怎么 你以为都是持枪抢劫犯
What, you thought it was all gonna be armed robbers.
和心脏病复发什么的吗
and heart attacks waiting to happen?
- 她才十二岁 - 有严重的心脏病
- She's 12! - With a serious heart condition.
下一个是谁
Who's next on the list?
迪恩 你必须带她走
Dean, you have to take her.
- 谁说的 - 死亡骑士
- Says who? - Death.
- 我就是死亡骑士 - 你明白我的意思
- I'm death. - You know what I mean.
那又是谁让他这么做的
Well, who tells him?
我不知道 一切本该如此
I don't know. It just is.
这是命运
It's destiny.
歇歇吧
Give me a break.
我这辈子都在和命运抗争
I've spent my whole life fighting that crap.
根本没有什么命运
There's no such thing as destiny,
就像根本没有世界末日一样
just like there was no apocalypse …
不过是一堆狂妄的混蛋
Just a bunch of stuck-up mooks.
不想让我们人类奴隶对他们质疑罢了
who didn't want us human slaves asking questions.
我要让这小女孩活着
Well, I say the little girl lives.
你知道有趣之处在哪里吗
Do you know what's amazing?
你说的这些连你自己都不相信
You don't actually buy a word you're saying.
- 才没有 - 是吗
- Yes, I do. - Oh, really?
所以每次你们干预那些生生死死的事
So, all the times that you messed with life and death,
结果都很顺心是吗
they just worked out for you?
每次都像开沙滩派对一样欢乐 是吗
It was just a beach party every time, huh?
我只知道
Well, I know this much …
我是死亡骑士 她十二岁
I'm death, she's 12,
她今天不会死
and she's not dying today.
从医学角度上 我解释不了
Medically, I can't explain it.
所以她的心脏就痊愈了吗
So her heart just healed?
有时候
Couple of times in your career,
确实会遇到一些事 只能称之为奇迹
you see something you just got to call a miracle.
我只知道不需要动手术了
All I know is I won't have to operate.
谢谢 谢谢你 医生
Thank you. Thank you, doctor.
你做到了 你会没事的
You did it. You're gonna be okay.
亲爱的 你猜怎么样 我要下班了
Hey, hon, guess what? I'm leaving.
不是 手术取消了
No, surgery was canceled.
走吧 这里还有别的活
Come on. We have more work here.
好 一会儿见
Okay. See you soon.
对A
Pair of aces.
再来一杯吗
Want another one?
当然
Yeah, sure.
姜还是老的辣 你还太嫩了小子
May have been born at night, boy, but it wasn't last night.
糟糕
Not good.
萨姆 咱可想清楚了再动手
Let's not do anything hasty here, Sam.
不用说「强尼来了哦」（《闪灵》中的台词）
Don't say, "Here's Johnny."
我必须这样做 鲍比 抱歉
I got to do this, Bobby. I'm sorry.
你不该把自己逼入绝境
You shouldn't have cornered yourself.
我没有
I didn't!
加固的钢芯钛踢板
Reinforced steel core, titanium kick plate.
惬意享受吧
Get comfy.
你不想给我解释下吗
You want to explain what this is about?
我只是
I just, uh…
迫于无奈 鲍比
I have to do this, Bobby.
你坑爹呢
Says who?
要是迪恩把灵魂塞回我的身体
If Dean shoves that soul back in me,
想像下那会多可怕
think how bad that could really be.
我必须阻止他 鲍比
I can't let it happen, Bobby.
说真的 我不想杀你
I mean, it's not like I want to kill you.
你一直都对我很好
You've been nothing but good to me.
所以呢
So…what,
你跟恶魔做了交易还是咋的
demon deal or something?
是个咒语
Spell.
你这是在发昏 萨姆
You're making a mistake, Sam.
我只想好好的活下去
I'm trying to survive.
迪恩已经找了个妥善的方法
Dean's got a way to make it safe.
是啊 什么在我脑中制造屏障之类的
Oh, yeah, what, some wall inside my head.
可能屹立不倒 扯淡吧
that maybe stays up? Come on.
那或许行得通
If it works …
要是行不通呢
Yeah, what if it doesn't?
迪恩一点不在乎我
Dean doesn't care about me.
他只关心他的那个
He … he just cares about his little brother, Sammy,
还在地狱里受罪小萨姆
burning in hell.
他为了把那个人弄回来简直在所不惜
He'll kill me to get that other guy back.
听着
Look, I…
我知道这很可怕
I know how scary it is.
但你知道什么更可怕吗
But you know what's scarier?
是现在的你
You right now.
你头脑不清醒 萨姆
You're not in your right head, Sam.
你让我们没的选
You're not giving us much choice here.
萨姆
Sam?
操蛋
Balls!
别想在太岁爷头上动土
Ain't nobody killing me in my house but me.
我虽不情愿 但必要时一样会炸了你的腿
I don't want to blow your legs out, boy, but I will.
是怎样 你现在跟我搞冷战啊
Oh, what, you gonna give me the silent treatment now?
来真的
Really?
真该死 我就知道
Damn it! I knew it!
怎么了
What?
编号500 请到急诊室
Code 500, E.R.
怎么回事
What's going on?
脊柱挫伤 内出血
Fractured spine, internal bleeding.
在救护车上心脏病发作
Had a heart attack in the ambulance.
- 欧文斯医生呢 - 他刚离开
- We need Dr. Owens. - He just left.
打给他 让他赶紧回来
Call Owens. Tell him to turn around.
- 血压多少 - 血压60/30
- BP? - BP's 60 over 30.
注射一毫克青霉素V钾
Push one milligram of vepen.
- 等等 那是 - 你没带走那女孩
- Wait, that's… - You let the girl live.
护士提早回家
The nurse goes home early,
发生了本不应该发生的车祸
gets in a crash she wouldn't have.
现在她需要心脏外科医生
And she needs the heart surgeon,
他在哪里
and where is he?
你早料到会这样
You knew this would happen?
没有
No.
我只知道你引发了一连串事件
Just knew that you knocked over a domino.
加油啊 约琳
Come on, Jolene.
她心跳骤停了
She's in cardiac arrest.
- 带她走 - 什么
- Take her. - What?
准备
Clear!
但她不在名单上
She's not on the list!
有因必有果
Everything you do has consequences.
你还想引起其它的连锁反应吗
Do you want to set off another chain reaction?
那也跟她毫无关系
She's got nothing to do with this!
真是糟糕 迪恩
Well, too bad, Dean.
你戴上了戒指 就认命的干活吧
You put on the ring. Now do your damn job.
- 好了 - 准备
- Go. - Clear!
好吧
Fine.
她快不行了
She is not gonna make it.
心脏停跳 她快不行了
She's crashing again. We're losing her.
300伏 充电
300, charging.
- 准备 - 好了
- Clear! - Here we go.
- 没有反应 - 那是
- No response. - Is that…
- 我是… - 是的
- Am I… - Yes.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
但我还
But I'm…
还很年轻
So young.
没错
Yeah.
你本应长命百岁
Actually, you were supposed to live for many decades.
生孩子 抱孙子
Have kids, grandkids.
那为什么
Then why?
因为他搞砸了
Because he screwed up.
都是因为你吗
You did this to me?
走吧 约琳 时候到了
Come on, Jolene. It's time.
等等
Wait.
对不起
I'm sorry.
她在哪儿 我妻子在哪儿
Where is she? Where's my wife?
在哪里
Where is she?
天啊 等等
God, wait.
不
No!
一次真正的假期吗
A real vacation?
没错
Yeah.
我能带你去这家咖啡厅
I can take you to this one cafe,
带你看我在哪里遇见了你母亲
show you where I met your mom.
你看到发生在护士身上的事了
You saw what happened to the nurse.
去带走那孩子吧 迪恩
Go and kill that girl, Dean.
我想说的你都明白
I tried to tell you what you already know.
她现在还活着
She's disrupting the natural order.
就是扰乱了自然秩序
by being alive.
你最清楚那意味着什么
You of all people know what that means.
她的余生将在混乱与悲伤中度过
Chaos and sadness will follow her for the rest of her life.
你的方法我们试过了
We tried it your way.
给我一点时间
Give me a minute.
什么
What?
赶紧的 兄弟 靠边停车
Come on, man, pull the car over.
不然就搭上小命了
You're gonna get yourself killed.
干什么呢 叫你靠边停车
What are you doing? Pull the damn car over!
停车
Stop the car.
快给我停车
Come on, stop the car.
脑子糨糊了吧 停车
What are you doing?! Stop the car!
管他娘的
Son of a bitch.
- 鬼啊 - 踩刹车
- Aah! - Hit the brakes!
该死
Damn it.
苔莎
Tessa!
你在吗 苔莎
You there?! Tessa?!
我输了
I lost!
萨姆的事黄了
Sam's screwed!
高兴了吧
You happy?!
至少你能把我瞬移回家吧
Least you can do is zap my ass back home!
听见没
Hello?!
我赌输了
I lost the bet.
对你弟弟深表遗憾
Sorry about your brother.
我们走吧
Let's just go.
去哪儿 迪恩 交易结束了
Go where, Dean? We're done.
我们
What are we …
结束未完的工作
Unfinished business.
一切都结束了
It's over.
你摘下了戒指
You took the ring off.
不管怎样 我以为你想让这女孩逃过一劫
Anyway, I thought you wanted the girl to skate by.
不 没人逃得过去
No one really skates by.
不是吗
Do they?
该告别了 哥们
You should say your goodbyes, man.
喂 宝贝
Hey, honey.
我一定是打瞌睡了
I must have dozed off.
希拉里
Hilary?
快来人啊
Somebody!
一 二 三
One, two, three,
没反应 没有脉搏
Nothing, not getting a pulse.
一 二 三
One, two, three,
我死了吗
I'm dead?
很遗憾
I'm sorry.
- 那我爸爸怎么办 - 他会没事的
- But what about my dad? - He'll be fine.
真的吗
Really?
我也不清楚
I have no idea.
我不能丢下他
I-I can't just leave him.
- 太不公平了 - 我知道
- It's not fair! - I know.
那为什么还要这样
Well, then why?
因为
Because…
万物皆有其秩序
There's sort of a … a natural order to things.
秩序什么的都是狗屁
Natural order is stupid.
我也这么觉得
Well, I agree with you there.
听我说
Listen to me.
你不想这么做的
You don't want to do this.
萨姆
Sam.
我像你亲爹一样待你 孩子
I've been like a father to you, boy.
你心里必须明白这点
Somewhere inside, you've got to know that.
好了 就这样吧
Well, that's just it.
抱歉
Sorry.
嗨 萨姆 我回来了
Hi, sam. I'm back.
我不能一直这样 鲍比
I can't keep doing this, Bobby.
是要我怎样
I mean, what am I,
每次他要杀人的时候都把他捆起来吗
gonna tie him up every time he tries to kill someone?
那也困不住他 他…
And that's not gonna hold him. I mean, he's …
什么都做得出
Capable of anything.
我该怎么办
What am I supposed to do here?
我不知道
I don't know.
迪恩
Dean.
来 一起
Join me.
给你带了个…
Brought you one …
从洛杉矶那家有名的
From a little stand in Los Angeles.
培根热狗店买的
known for their bacon dogs.
坐
Sit.
天 怎么吃上这么廉价的东西了
Boy, what's with you and cheap food?
彼此彼此啊
I could ask you the same thing.
想在戴回戒指前先好好犒劳自己一下
Thought I'd have a treat before I put the ring back on.
比你想象的难 对吧
Heavier than it looks, isn't it?
有时候 你真的只想摆脱这东西
Sometimes, you just want the thing off.
但也只能想想了
But you know that.
不饿吗
Not hungry?
听着
Look…
我想你知道我失败了
I think you know that I flunked.
给你吧
So there.
顺便提一下 我
Oh, and by the way, I, uh…
干你的活儿 我糟透了
I sucked at being you.
把自然秩序什么的搞得一塌糊涂
Really screwed up the whole natural order thing.
不过我相信你也已经知道了
But I'm sure you knew about that, too.
那么 如果时间倒流
So, if you could go back,
你会就直接杀了那个小女孩吗
would you simply kill the little girl?
不再婆妈又傲娇
No fuss, no stomping your feet?
如果知道是这么回事 我会的
Knowing what I know now, yeah.
这话还真让我吃惊
I'm surprised to hear that.
有惊 也有喜
Surprised and glad.
随便吧 别太激动
Yeah, well, don't get excited.
我会救下那个护士
I would have saved the nurse, okay?
就这样
That's it.
我想不光是这样吧
I think it's a little more than that.
今天 你见识到了生死之事如何运作
Today, you got a hard look behind the curtain.
扰乱自然秩序可不好玩
Wrecking the natural order's not quite such fun.
尤其在你还要亲自承担后果的时候 对吗
when you have to mop up the mess, is it?
这对你来说很难 迪恩
This is hard for you, Dean.
你随便舍弃自己的性命 因为你觉得
You throw away your life because you've come to assume.
反正还能捡回来
that it'll bounce right back into your lap.
但人的灵魂可不是橡皮球
But the human soul is not a rubber ball.
它并不持久 还很脆弱
It's vulnerable, impermanent,
但却比你想象的强大
but stronger than you know.
也远比你想象中的珍贵
And more valuable than you can imagine.
那么
So…
我想你今天学到了些东西
I think you've learned something today.
想知道我怎么想吗
Want to know what I think?
我想你早料到我一天都坚持不下来
I think you knew that I wouldn't last a day.
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
我输了 我认了
I lost. Fine.
但至少我还有胆量承认
But at least I have the balls to admit.
这从一开始就有猫腻儿
that it was rigged from the jump.
多数人跟我说话的时候都会恭敬些
Most people speak to me with more respect.
我不是那意思
I didn't mean …
就说到这吧
We're done here.
非常愉快
It's been lovely.
但现在我要回到地狱去
But now I'm going to go to hell.
去拿回你弟弟的灵魂
to get your brother's soul.
你为什么要这么帮我
Why would you do that for me?
这不是为你
I wouldn't do it for you.
你和你弟弟不断地复活
You and your brother keep coming back.
你们的存在是宇宙平衡的奇耻大辱
You're an affront to the balance of the universe,
你们造成了整个世界的混乱
and you cause disruption on a global scale.
我很抱歉
I apologize for that.
但你还有用处
But you have use.
现在 你在调查某事
Right now, you're digging at something.
英勇无畏的大侦探
The intrepid detective.
我要你继续调查 迪恩
I want you to keep digging, Dean.
那你不跟我说说明白吗
So you're just gonna be cryptic, or…
这事关灵魂
It's about the souls.
该明白的时候你会明白的
You'll understand when you need to.
等等
Wait …
关于萨姆
With Sam…
屏障那东西真的有用吗
is this wall thing really gonna work?
75%的几率吧
Call it 75%.
鲍比
Bobby!
开门
Open the door.
- 怎么了 - 快
- What happened? - Now!
离我远点
Get away from me!
不要
Don't.
Don't!
听着 萨姆
Now, sam,
我将在你的意识里放入一个屏障
I'm gonna put up a barrier inside your mind.
不 别碰我
No, don't touch me.
你可能会感到有些…痒
It might feel a little…itchy.
但帮我个忙
But do me a favor …
不要碰这个屏障
Don't scratch the wall.
因为 相信我
Because trust me …
你不会喜欢那后果
You're not gonna like what happens.
求你了
Please.
别这么做
Don't do this.
不 不要 你不知道
No, no! You don't know!
你不知道到底会发生什么
You don't know what'll happen to me!
求你
Please.
不 不要
No, no…